Aaron Fritz Santos

Marikina, National Capital Region, Philippines



afsaints@yahoo.com



+639958613015



linkedin.com/in/afsaints0987

Summary

With more than 10 years of experience in Aviation Industry. I have a good problem solving skills and decision making, I can do multi-task work with minimum supervision and under pressure. I have a sufficient computer technical skills since I work most of the time facing the computer.

I am a team player, handling a team and working in a team is one of my strength. I manage my time wisely as I can work fast and also I'm a fast learner I am motivated if I learn new things and skills as it adds up on my self-development as well as inside my resume.

As of the moment I'm currently learning to be a Web Developer, I have a basic understanding on HTML5, CSS3, Javascipt, PHP, MySQL and Bootstrap and willing to learn more.

Experience



Freelance Web Designer

Freelance

Jun 2020 - Present (7 months +)

Creating basic web pages and landing pages using HTML5 and CSS3

- ^o Basic background in Javascript
- Observe of the second of th
- ^o Basic understanding in MYSQL relational database management system.
- ° Currently learning Python programming language

Customer Service Officer

dnata

Oct 2014 - Jun 2020 (5 years 9 months)

Part of the Emirates Group, dnata is one of the world's largest air services providers offering ground handling, cargo, travel, and flight catering services across five continents. I was assigned at Customer Service Department doing the following:

- Our Handling flights for Emirates Airline and Myanmar Airways Int'l.
- ^o Working as a Flight Controller doing daily report, coordinating with other department (Catering services, Baggage Services, Load Control)
- ^o Supervising at least 10 people in the team and doing daily briefing for the day's flight.
- ^o Reporting to our immediate supervisor/ duty manager in regards about incidents and other things happen on the flight.

Customer Service Assistant

Nov 2011 - Oct 2014 (3 years)

- ^o Doing ground handling duties on check-in, departure and arrival on various airlines.
- Work as a lounge staff accommodating our premium passengers (First, Business and Frequent Flyer
- o Handles VIP's on various airlines.
- ^o Work with around 10-15 people on the team

Customer Service Agent

PAGSS Inc.

Jul 2008 - Oct 2011 (3 years 4 months)

- ^o Doing ground handling duties such as check-in, departure and arrival services.
- ^o Handle baggage cases such as missing, pilferage and damaged baggage
- o Handle flights for EVA Airways.

Education



🔣 University of Santo Tomas

Bachelor of Science (BS), Tourism and Travel Services Management 2004 - 2008

Skills

Customer Service • Airlines • Microsoft Office • Aviation • Customer Satisfaction • Commercial Aviation • Airports • Civil Aviation • Web Development • Responsive Web Design